To all my gym
girlies
I just found your
new gym bestie
Regular creatine felt like
a toxic relationship
Clumpy bland and just
sat there in my
glass and in my
routine
Didn't mix didn't absorb
didn't help
But then I switched
to Muscle Blaze creatine
It is clinically tested
to absorb more than
39% from regular creatine
No clumps no extra
carbs no weird mixing
Drama
In just two three
weeks I could feel
the difference
Motion during lips less
soreness and faster recovery
Now I don't have
to fake progress just
for the gram
I can actually feel
it in my lifts
my body and my
energy
Muscle Blaze Micronized Creatine
Monohydrate Cream is the
new gym bestie I
have ever needed